That has
happened
Om Om
[Music]
Hello friends, a very warm welcome to all of
you on my YouTube channel, I am your
help till tomorrow Kajal. Today's video is a very
important video. Today in this video I am
going to share with you an
incident which happened recently with our marriage.
So let's start the video.
Our viewers are Sameeksha. She
called me yesterday and told me that we had taken an insurance plan from a well-known company, a
company which is one of the top 5 companies.
In 2018, she took this policy online
from a broker. The form was also filled online over the
phone after asking all the details from them.
They told everything was correct and the
form has to be filled but I don't know whether the person with whom I got the
policy done was successful
or not. You know, when you take a health policy online,
you face a lot of problems.
You don't know how much knowledge that person has.
Or if the bill is
coming, ask this question. Due to being positive, you
are admitted in the hospital and
after getting discharged, you
need a computer file for the deep hospital bill tubeless minute.
Now, after getting discharged from the hospital, when you go to
your home,  He came to file for his beloved Vashishtha.
During that time
some people from the company
came to his house for inspection. Regarding obscene zone-5, the
form was made to be filled by him. He further
wrote in the subscriber's name. He
filled the form with his own hands. He
also wrote everything truthfully in the column of pre-existing wages.
This form was given to him to update the details.
Even after telling the truth, the company rejected his claim
saying that you have
hidden your pre-existing Rishi from the company.
By showing pre-existing disease as non-disclosure, the company set the language of this.
See where is his mistake? Find out, he took a
health insurance policy of Dainik Bhaskar online
and Spain cheated him. That
person hid his pre-existing Rishi from this company.
See, how big a fraud has happened
with this person, that is why we repeatedly tell you people
not to buy online health policy
and otherwise, a lot happens to you. You do
not find any real and knowledgeable person here
that percent  What was their mistake? They did not want to take the policy by lying to the company
or hiding some disease,
but still something was done to
them. They took a
health insurance policy in their name by lying to the company and
you had to bear the loss. After paying for it for free for many years, the
insurance was cancelled at the time of need.
Their only mistake was
that they took the policy by trusting some unknown person online. To prevent this from happening to
me and Onion tomorrow,
you can
set an alarm online. But you must
always remember this thing. Why would someone harm you by
giving you a health policy at a low premium?
You should never
fall into the greed of a cheap health policy. Always take a health policy based on
technology. Before that,
take it from a supported person who will
support you after the policy. Friends, if you found this
video of mine final, then please
subscribe to my channel, like my video
and click the bell icon and
share this video with your relatives as much as possible so that we all
together can save people from online SIM from Pune.
Thank you very much for staying with us in the video. Thanks for
watching this video.
[Music]